wallpaper-house.com 2019-10-20

# Wallpapers groups presented by wallpaper-house.com

[Check this link](http://kingcasinobonus.co.uk/new-casino-bonuses/) and get your hands on the best and biggest online casino promotions in the United Kingdom! Have fun playing top games!

## Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy for **https://wallpapers-house.com**

The privacy of our visitors to **https://wallpapers-house.com** is important to us.

At **https://wallpapers-house.com** , we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit **https://wallpapers-house.com** , and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

Log Files As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

Cookies and Web Beacons We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on **https://wallpapers-house.com** to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

**DoubleClick DART** cookies We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (“interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting https://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

## Disclaimer

If you have reason to believe that one of our content is violating your copyrights or some of Search Results references to illegal contents, please Contact Us using the contact menu we provide.

Please allow up to a 1-3 business days for an email response. Note that emailing your complaint to other parties such as our Internet Service Provider, Hosting Provider, and other third party will not expedite your request and may result in a delayed response due to the complaint not being filed properly.

**Required information**

Please note that we deal only with messages that meet the following requirements:

  * Please Provide us with your name, address and telephone number. We reserve the right to verify this information.
  * Explain which copyrighted material is affected.
  * Please provide the exact and complete to the URL link.
  * If it a case of files with illegal contents, please describe the contents briefly in two or three points.
  * Please ensure that you can receive further inquiries from us at the e-mail address you are writing from.
  * Please write to us only in English.

**Notice:**

Anonymous or incomplete messages will not be dealt with. Thank you for your understanding.

**Disclaimer:**

All the images are not under our Copyrights and belong to their respective owners. We respect Copyright Laws. If You have found the link to an illegal content, please report it to us using the contact menu. We will remove it in 1-3 business days.

Thank you!
